export interface Question {
  id: number;
  day: number;
  question: string;
  answer: string;
  message: string;
}

export const questions: Question[] = [
  {
    id: 1,
    day: 1,
    question: "What day is today?👂☝️",
    answer: "Monday",
    message: "No, its not monday...its NITHARSHANA'S DAY...HAPPYYYY BIRTHHDAYYY NGAAA!💙"
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    day: 2,
    question: "In which class did we first meet?",
    answer: "8",
    message: "Haha! Ofcourse its 8th grade. Miss the old days huh? ✨"
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    day: 3,
    question: "Which TV show i recommended you to watch and you loved it?(ofcourse there are many but this is the most popular one)",
    answer: "stranger things",
    message: "Whenever i watch Stranger things, i think about you and how you will react to certain scenes...lol! 😅"
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    day: 4,
    question: "What's my biggest fear?",
    answer: "Losing people",
    message: "WOW! You remembered!? Quite surprised..lol 🤐"
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    day: 5,
    question: "whats my favorite colour?",
    answer: "Blue",
    message: "Tell me you got this in your first try lol, if not i hate you😭"
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    day: 6,
    question: "who broke our snapstreak?",
    answer: "nitharshana",
    message: "ofc you did bitch!👊"
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    day: 7,
    question: "who is your favorite cousin?(nicknames only)",
    answer: "reenu",
    message: "I hope she is your favorite or else im dead lol😂"
  },
   {
    id: 8,
    day: 8,
    question: "Who is the most bitchy one between us?",
    answer: "sanjay",
    message: "Well yeah , i agree its on me but i wonder if this took you two attempts?🙂‍↕️"
  },
   {
    id: 9,
    day: 9,
    question: "Eminem or talyor?",
    answer: "Eminem",
    message: "hehee....if you need crt answer you have to type eminem and yk why? cuz hes better than her booo..😈"
  },
   {
    id: 10,
    day: 10,
    question: "Who carries more guilt: (A) - the heart that follows love or (B) - the heart that lets love go? ",
    answer: "A",
    message: "lol answer to that question might change from person to person but yea anyways someone is gonna carry guilt thats life i believe whatever. You made it to the end... today is the last day....i will miss you😩...GOODBYE!\n\n ____GAME OVER____"
  }
];